Finding Aid for Horace H. Rackham School of Graduate Studies (University of Michigan) Records, 1892-2014
Bentley Historical Library, University of Michigan
- Faculty Fellowships, Grants and Awards
  - International Partnerships Program
    - Forms and Guidelines (Box 151)
    - Individual Progress Reports, 1980 (Box 151)
    - Selection Committee Membership List, 1980-1985 (Box 151)
    - Summary Lists, 1980-1983 (Box 151)
    - Competition, 1979-1980 (Box 151)
    - Competition, 1980-1981 (Box 151)
    - Competition, 1982 (Box 151)
    - Competition, 1983 (Box 151)
    - Competition, 1984 (Box 151)
    - Competition, 1985 (Box 151)
    - Competition, 1986 (Box 151)
    - Competition, 1987 (Box 151)
  - Raoul Wallenberg Medal and Lecture
    The Raoul Wallenberg Medal and Lecture sub series (0.5 linear foot) encompasses files which document each lecture given between 1990 and 1995. The award was inaugurated in the Autumn of 1990, as the result of a university-wide effort to establish a tribute to Raoul Wallenberg. Wallenberg, a 1935 alumnus of the university's architecture program, saved tens of thousands of Jews in Hungary during the final years of WWII. He survived the Nazis, but disappeared into the Soviet gulag in 1945 and his whereabouts are unknown, although he is now presumed dead. The award and lectureship is bestowed annually by a committee which selects a contemporary humanitarian of international stature, "whose achievements embody Wallenberg's selfless commitment." Past recipients include Elie Wiesel, Miep Gies, Per Anger, and Tenzin Gyatso, the Dali Lama.
    - Background and development of award, circa 1985-1988 (Box 152)
    - Past Awardees
      - Elie Wiesel (1990) (Box 152)
      - Jan Karski (1991) (Box 152)
      - Helen Suzman (1992) (Box 152)
      - Tenzin Gyatso, Dali Lama (1993-1994) (Box 152)
      - Miep Gies (1994-1995) (Box 152)
      - Per Anger (1995-1996) (Box 152)
      - Marion Pritchard (1996-1997) (Box 152)
  - Rackham and University, 1920-1998
    The Rackham and University awards subseries (0.5 linear feet) spans the years from 1920 to 1998. The subseries contains general materials and recipient listings relating to various faculty grants, fellowships, and awards funded by Rackham or the University of Michigan, arranged alphabetically by award title. There is one folder of general statistical data regarding these faculty awards. Also included here are listings of recipients of Fulbright (1984-1986) and Guggenheim Foundation (1981-1986 and 1993) awards.
    - Amoco Foundation Faculty Teaching Awards, Recipients Dossiers,1998 (Box 154)
    - "Announcement of Rackham Programs to Support Faculty Research and Other Creative Activities,", 1986/1987-1991/1992 (Box 154)
    - Application Revisions, 1986-1990 (Box 154)
    - Awards for Research Scientists, 1989 (Box 154)
    - Distinguished Faculty Achievement Award
      - Listing of Recipients, 1955-1987 (Box 154)
      - Information and Recipients Dossiers, 1998 (Box 154)
    - Distinguished University Professors, Listing of Active Recipients, 1987 (Box 154)
    - Eligibility for Funding Senior Faculty, 1984-1990 (Box 154)
    - Faculty Recognition Awards
      - Listing of Recipients, 1959-1987 (Box 154)
      - Information and Recipients Dossiers, 1998 (Box 154)
    - Faculty Research Development Program, 1976; 1978 (Box 154)
    - Gender Research Fellowship, 1983-1986 (Box 154)
    - Henry Russell Award, Listing of Recipients, 1925-1988 (Box 154)
    - Michigan Memorial-Phoenix Project, 1988-1989 (Box 154)
    - Named Professorships, Listing, 1920-1996; as of 1987 (Box 154)
    - Office of Vice-President for Graduate Studies and Research (OVPR) Funding, 1983-1989 (Box 154)
    - Research Partnership Program, 1986-1988 (Box 154)
    - Statistical Data, 1971-1994 (Box 154)
  - Outside Funding, 1981-1993
    - Fulbright, Listing of Recipients, 1984-1986 (Box 154)
    - Guggenheim Foundation, Listing of Recipients, 1981-1986; 1993 (Box 154)
- Graduate School Executive Board and Administrative Council
  The Executive Board series (19.3 linear feet) spans the years from 1892 to 1996. The series includes correspondence; materials to Board elections; and minutes, agendas, and supporting documents. The "Correspondence and Miscellaneous" subseries includes correspondence, board minutes, memos and other materials pertaining to Executive Board functioning, arranged chronologically. "Elections," includes general materials pertaining to nomination and election of Executive and Divisional Board members, arranged chronologically, as well as ballot counts and membership rosters.
  The bulk of the series (18 linear feet) is comprised of agendas, minutes, and supporting materials from Rackham Executive Board and Administrative Council meetings from 1892 to 1990. The minutes from 1892 through 1971 are held in bound volumes, while minutes and documents from 1971 through 1990 are unbound.
  - Correspondence and Miscellaneous, 1945-1991
    - 1945-1971 (Box 153)
    - 1971-1991, 20 folders (Box 153)
  - Elections, 1949-1996
    - Ballot Counts, 1973-1989 (Box 153)
    - Membership, Executive and Divisional Boards, 1971-1987 (Box 153)
    - Membership, Nominating Committee, 1949-1986 (Box 153)
    - General
      - 1971-1990, 23 folders (Box 153)
      - 1991-1996, 7 folders (Box 154)
  - Administrative Council Minutes (Bound Volumes)
    - (A), October 1, 1892-June 17, 1897 (Box 155)
    - (B), October 11, 1897-November 3, 1902 (Box 155)
    - (C), February 17, 1903-June 29, 1908 (Box 155)
    - (D), October 5, 1908-September 30, 1912 (Box 155)
  - Executive Board Minutes (Bound Volumes)
    - (E) (with index), June 29, 1912-July 13, 1915 (Box 155)
    - (F) (with index), September 21, 1915-August 4, 1919 (Box 155)
    - (G) (with index), September 23, 1919-July 15, 1925 (Box 155)
    - (H) (with index), October 6, 1925-December 16, 1930 (Box 155)
    - (I) (with index), February 26, 1931-June 14, 1934 (Box 155)
    - (J) (with index), October 9, 1934-July 29, 1936 (Box 156)
    - (K) (with index), September 30, 1936-June 16, 1937 (Box 156)
    - (L) (with index), September 29, 1937-June 22, 1938 (Box 156)
    - (M) (with index), July 29, 1938-June 16, 1939 (Box 156)
    - (N) (with index), October 4, 1939-June 12, 1940 (Box 156)
    - (O) (with index), October 2, 1940-June 18, 1941 (Box 156)
    - (P) (with index), October 1, 1941-August 5, 1942 (Box 156)
    - (Q) (with index), October 7, 1942-May 27, 1943 (Box 156)
    - (R) (with index), September 1, 1943-June 28, 1944 (Box 156)
    - (S) (with index), November 8, 1944-June 20, 1945 (Box 156)
    - (T) (with index), July 11, 1945-June 19, 1946 (Box 157)
    - (U) (with index), August 14, 1946-June 4, 1947 (Box 157)
    - (V) (with index), July 23, 1947-June 2, 1948 (Box 157)
    - (W) (with index), July 7, 1948-June 1, 1949 (Box 157)
    - (X) (with index), September 13, 1949-May 31, 1950 (Box 157)
    - (Y) (with index), September 27, 1950-May 23, 1951 (Box 157)
    - (Z) (with index), September 26, 1951-May 28, 1952 (Box 157)
    - (AA) (with index), July 25, 1952-May 27, 1953 (Box 158)
    - (BB) (with index), September 23, 1953-June 14, 1954 (Box 158)
    - (CC) (with index), September 22, 1954-June 1, 1955 (Box 158)
    - (DD) (with index), July 20, 1955-May 23, 1956 (Box 158)
    - (EE) (with index), September 26, 1956-May 29, 1957 (Box 158)
    - (FF) (with index), September 25, 1957-May 28, 1958 (Box 159)
    - (GG) (with index), September 24, 1958-May 27, 1959 (Box 159)
    - (HH) (with index), July 31, 1959-May 25, 1960 (Box 159)
    - (II) (with index), July 13, 1960-May 31, 1961 (Box 159)
    - (JJ) (with index), July 26, 1961-June 29, 1962 (Box 159)
    - (KK) (with index), September 10, 1962-June 26, 1963 (Box 159)
    - (LL) (with index), September 4, 1963-June 17, 1964 (Box 160)
    - (MM) (with index), September 2, 1964-June 23, 1965 (Box 160)
    - (NN) (with index), September 1, 1965-June 8, 1966 (Box 160)
    - (OO) (with index), July 20, 1966-June 21, 1967 (Box 160)
    - (PP) (with index), July 26, 1967-April 17, 1968
      - Agendas and Discussion Documents (Box 160)
    - (QQ) (with index), September 4, 1968-June 25, 1969 (Box 161)
    - (RR) (with index), September 10, 1969-May 1, 1970 (Box 161)
    - (SS) (with index), July 13, 1970-May 19, 1971 (Box 161)
  - Executive Board Minutes, Agendas, and Documents (Unbound)
    - Executive Board Document Lists, 1971/1972-, 1989-1990; 2 folders (Box 161)
    - 1971-1972
      - Minutes, 1971-1972 (Box 161)
      - Executive Board Documents #1-10, 1971-1972 (Box 161)
      - Executive Board Documents #11-65, 1971-1972; 4 folders (Box 162)
    - 1972-1973
      - Minutes, 1972-1973 (Box 162)
      - Executive Board Documents #1-52, 1972-1973; 5 folders (Box 162)
      - Miscellaneous Executive Board Documents, 1972-1973; 2 folders (Box 162)
    - 1973-1974
      - Minutes and Agendas, 1973-1974 (Box 163)
      - Executive Board Documents #1-68, 1973-1974; 8 folders (Box 163)
    - 1974-1975
      - Minutes and Agendas, 1974-1975 (Box 163)
      - Executive Board Documents #1-30dd, 1974-1975; 3 folders (Box 163)
      - Executive Board Documents #31-79, 1974-1975; 3 folders (Box 164)
    - 1975-1976
      - Agenda Items (no Minutes), 1975-1976 (Box 164)
      - Miscellaneous, 1975-1976 (Box 164)
      - Executive Board Documents #1-43, 1975-1976; 4 folders (Box 164)
    - 1976-1977
      - [No Minutes or Agendas 1976/77] (Box 164)
      - Executive Board Documents #1-12, 1976-1977 (Box 164)
      - Executive Board Documents #13-75, 1976-1977; 4 folders (Box 165)
    - 1977-1978
      - Minutes and Agendas, 1977-1978 (Box 165)
      - Executive Board Documents #1-97, 1977-1978; 6 folders (Box 165)
      - Executive Board Retreat Documents, 1977-1978 (Box 166)
    - 1978-1979
      - Minutes and Agendas, 1978-1979 (Box 166)
      - Executive Board Documents #1-87, 1978-1979; 9 folders (Box 166)
    - 1979-1980
      - Minutes and Agendas, 1979-1980 (Box 167)
      - Executive Board Documents #1-76, 1979-1980; 11 folders (Box 167)
    - 1980-1981
      - Minutes and Agenda, 1980-1981 (Box 167)
      - Executive Board Documents #1-7, 1980-1981 (Box 167)
      - Executive Board Documents #8-58, 1980-1981; 6 folders (Box 168)
    - 1981-1982
      - Minutes and Agendas, 1981-1982 (Box 168)
      - Executive Board Documents #1-66, 1981-1982; 5 folders (Box 168)
    - 1982-1983
      - Minutes and Agendas, 1982-1983 (Box 168)
      - Executive Board Documents #1-6, 1982-1983 (Box 168)
      - Executive Board Documents #7-57, 1982-1983; 5 folders (Box 169)
        - Response to the Critique and Recommendations from the Rackham Reviews of the Graduate Programs of the University of Michigan School of Nursing (Box 169)
    - 1983/, 1984
      - Minutes and Agendas, 1983-1984 (Box 169)
      - Executive Board Documents #1-80, 1983-1984; 6 folders (Box 169)
    - 1983-1984
      - Minutes and Agendas, 1984-1985 (Box 170)
      - Executive Board Documents #1-66, 1984-1985; 9 folders (Box 170)
    - 1985-1986
      - Minutes and Agendas, 1985-1986 (Box 170)
      - Executive Board Documents #1-35, 1985-1986; 4 folders (Box 170)
      - Executive Board Documents #36-56, 1985-1986; 3 folders (Box 171)
    - 1986-1987
      - Minutes and Agendas, 1986-1987 (Box 171)
      - Executive Board Documents #1-55, 1986-1987; 6 folders (Box 171)
    - 1987-1988
      - Minutes and Agendas, 1987-1988 (Box 171)
      - Executive Board Documents #1-44, 1987-1988; 3 folders (Box 171)
      - Executive Board Documents #45-54, 1987-1988 (Box 172)
    - 1988-1989
      - Minutes and Agendas, 1988-1989 (Box 172)
      - Executive Board Documents #1-42, 1988-1989; 4 folders (Box 172)
    - 1989-1990
      - Minutes and Agendas, 1989-1990 (Box 172)
      - Executive Board Documents #1-43, 1989-1990; 4 folders (Box 172)
  - Executive Board Minutes, Agendas, and Documents [Electronic]
    The Executive Board Minutes, Agendas, and Documents 1990-2005, are an extension of paper materials in the Graduate School Executive Board and Administrative Council series These documents consist of meeting agendas, minutes, and supporting materials and have been digitized by staff in the Dean's Office. The 1990-2003 files are scanned copies of paper originals. Beginning in 2004 the records are "born digital" files.
    - 1999-2003
      (87198_0001)
      [ER RESTRICTED until July 1, 2030 ]
    - 2003-2004
      (87198_0002)
      [ER RESTRICTED until July 1, 2031 ]
    - 2004-2005
      (87198_0003)
      [ER RESTRICTED until July 1, 2032 ]
    - 2005-2006, .ZIP file
      [ER RESTRICTED until July 1,2033 ]
    - 2065-2076, .ZIP file
- Dean's Chronological Files, 1996-1999
  The Dean's Chronological Files series (1.5 linear feet) contains chronological outgoing correspondence from 1996 and mail logs for 1997 through 1999. The mail logs describe the mail received by the Dean and how it was handled, but do not include any of the incoming or outgoing correspondence.
  - Dean's Mail Log
    - 01/23/1999-11/03/1999 (Box 181)
    - 1/98-1/22/99 (Box 181)
    - 05/1997-12/1997 (Box 181)
    - 1/97-4/97 (Box 181)
  - Correspondence, 1996; 11 folders (Box 182)
- Graduate Student Organizations
  The Graduate Student Organizations series consists of materials generated by or relating to various graduate student organizations. Subseries include Students of Color of Rackham (SCOR) and Panel on Allocation of Space for Student Organizations and University Involvement with Student Organizations.
  - Students of Color of Rackham (SCOR)
    The Students of Color of Rackham (SCOR) subseries contains two folders of correspondence and event flyers generated by this student group, which is a network for graduate and professional students dedicated to the social, cultural, and academic well being of students of color of African, Asian, Latino, and Native American descent. The material in this subseries gives a sense of the issues and events in which SCOR is interested, and the network of student organizations at the university related to issues of students of color. Additional information about SCOR can be found within the Associate Dean for Student Recruitment and Support Topical Files subseries and the Assistant Dean for Program Support series.
    - Correspondence and Flyers, 1994-1996; 2 folders (Box 190)
    - Annual Conference 15-18, 2005-2008; 2 folders (Box 196)
    - Cookbook, 2005-2006 (Box 196)
    - General, 2007 (Box 196)
    - Newsletter, 2005-2007 (Box 196)
  - Panel on Space Allocation for Student Organizations and University Involvement with Student Organizations, 2000
    The Panel on Allocation of Space for Student Organizations and University Involvement with Student Organizations series (1 linear foot) contains materials collected and generated by a special panel appointed by the President's Office in 2000 in response to a campus-wide controversy over the allocation of meeting and office space to student organizations. For a number of years, several groups on campus, including a controversial senior society called Michigamua, had held dedicated meeting rooms in the Michigan Union tower. In 2000, in a protest against Michigamua's use of Native American rituals and artifacts in their meetings and the university's perceived support for the group through the provision of dedicated meeting space, students from the Students of Color Coalition took over the tower rooms for five weeks from February 6 through March 13. Following the protest, President Bollinger announced the formation of the panel and charged it with examining two issues: 1) the University's policies and practices regarding space allocation to student organizations, with particular attention to whether any student organization should be entitled to space not subject to a periodic review process; and 2) the proper nature and scope of University involvement with student organizations. The panel's findings are included in this series, as are research materials, correspondence, and transcripts of two open forums held to gather public opinion.
    - Drafts and Correspondence (Box 191)
    - "Exposing the Michigamua" [printout of independent website] (Box 191)
    - Michigamua Information (Box 191)
    - "Notebook I-Space Allocation" (Box 191)
    - Organizational Notebook (Box 191)
    - Policies of Other Universities (Box 191)
    - Public Comments (Box 191)
    - Targeted E-mail (Box 191)
    - Transcripts from Open Forum, March 28, 2000 (Box 191)
    - Transcripts from Open Forum, April 9, 2000 (Box 191)
    - U-M Policies (Box 191)
- Events
  The Events series contains materials from a variety of social and educational events within Rackham, and includes audiovisual materials from many of these events.
  - A Conversation about Visas, 2005 (Box 232)
  - Accreditation Workshop, 1999 (Box 232)
  - At the Crossroads, 2000 (Box 232)
  - Atkins Conversation, 1993 (Box 232)
  - A/V Material
    - Audio Cassettes (Box 236)
      - Evenings at Rackham: Dr. Gilbert Omenn, 1998 (Box 236)
      - Future Series: David Scobey (Box 236)
      - Future Series: Jose-Marie Griffith (Box 236)
      - Lecture Series-John Cole, 1999 (Box 236)
    - VHS
      - A Conversation with Woman Provosts, 1999 (Box 236)
      - Evenings at Rackham Dr. Glibert Omenn, 1998 (Box 236)
      - Graduate Training and the Future of Higher Education, 1999 (Box 236)
      - Graduate Training and the Future of Higher Education, 1999 (Box 236)
      - I May Not Get There With You, 2001 (Box 236)
      - Meritocracy: The Late Debate with Nicholas Lemann, 1998 (Box 236)
      - Orientation, 1998 (Box 236)
      - Politics and the Research University: Lobbying for Higher Education, 1999 (Box 236)
      - Publishing in the Digital Age, 2001 (Box 236)
      - Robert Weisbuch, 1999 (Box 236)
      - The Body and Its Disciplines: From Cell to Self: Body -- Invoking Experience, 1999 (Box 236)
      - The Choice by Clare Luckham, 1999 (Box 236)
      - The Future of the Research University, 1999 (Box 236)
      - Through My Lens: Center for the Education of Women, 1997 (Box 236)
  - Betty Jean (Box 232)
    - Dean Jones, 1999 (Box 232)
    - Dedication Ceremony (VHS), 1999 (Box 232)
    - Memorial Dedication (Box 233)
    - Memorial Plaque, 1997 (Box 233)
    - Memorial Service (Box 233)
    - Professional Profile, 1996 (Box 233)
  - Bollinger Conversation, 1994 (Box 233)
  - Book Launchings, 1986-1994 (Box 233)
  - Budget and Finances, 1999 (Box 233)
  - Cohen Conversation, 1993 (Box 233)
  - Community Based Research Symposium, 2000 (Box 233)
  - Community Partnership Symposium, 2001 (Box 233)
  - Convocation/Opening Ceremony, 1989-1996 (Box 233)
  - CPP and Rackham Collaboration, 1999 (Box 233)
  - Dance for Mother Earth Pow Wow, 2004 (Box 233)
  - Dean's Reception, 1995 (Box 233)
  - Defense Science Study Group, 1995-2003 (Box 233)
  - Evenings at Rackham, 1994-1996 (Box 233)
  - Evenings at Rackham, 1998-2000 (Box 233)
  - Events at Rackham, Fall 1999 (Box 233)
  - Events at Rackham, Winter 1999 (Box 234)
  - Federalism and the Opportunity for all Children to Pursue a Quality Public School Education, 2004 (Box 234)
  - Gospel at Colonus Symposium, 1998-1999 (Box 234)
  - Graduate School Orientation, 1998-1999 (Box 234)
  - Gulf Symposium, 1991 (Box 234)
  - Holocaust Memorial, 1994 (Box 234)
  - I May Not Get There With You, 2001 (Box 234)
  - Interdisciplinary Institute, 1999; 2005 (Box 234)
  - June Meeting Roundtable, 2002 (Box 234)
  - Lecture Series, Fall 1998 (Box 234)
  - Lecture Series, Fall 1999 (Box 234)
  - Medical School/Rackham Lecture Collaborative Events, 2000 (Box 234)
  - Michigan Gospel Chorale, 2004 (Box 234)
  - Minority Graduate Education, 1999 (Box 234)
  - MQR Celebration, 2002 (Box 234)
  - Newsletter, 1991-2007 (Box 234)
  - OK/UM Exchange Partnership Program, 2004 (Box 235)
  - OVPR Retreat, 1998 (Box 235)
  - Partnerships Symposium, 2000 (Box 235)
  - Publishing in the Digital World, 2001; 2 folders (Box 235)
  - Rackham 50th Anniversary Symposium, 1988-1989 (Box 235)
  - Rackham Open House, 2004 (Box 235)
  - Rackham Reports, 1986-1991 (Box 235)
  - Rackham/Humanities Collaborative Program, 2005 (Box 235)
  - Receptions
    - Guggenheim Reception, 1996 (Box 235)
    - Postdoctoral Dinner, 1992-1996 (Box 235)
  - Rediscover Rackham, 2004 (Box 235)
  - Research Club Activities, 1995; 1998 (Box 235)
  - Responsive PhD Program, 2001 (Box 235)
  - Robert Weisbuch Luncheon (includes photos), 1996 (Box 235)
  - Sloan Grant Proposal, 1995-1996 (Box 235)
  - Student Activities Retreat, 2001 (Box 235)
  - Student Handbook of Policies and Procedures, 2002-2004 (Box 235)
  - Student Lounge (Box 235)
  - Talk of the Nation, 2001 (Box 235)
  - UM/Detroit Symposium, 2000 (Box 235)
- Grants, Fellowships, and Awards, 1989-2008
  The Grants, Fellowships, and Awards series includes three subseries: Awards, Grants, and Mellon Fellowship. The series pertains to grants and fellowships promoting scholarship and research as well as awards recognizing excellence in teaching. Types of grants include Graduate Assistance in Areas of National Need (GAANN), National Institutes of Health (NIH), National Aeronautics and Space Administration (NASA), and National Science Foundation (NSF). Materials include proposals, correspondence, award notices, and reports.
  - Awards, 1969-2007
    - 1969-2003
      - Academy Nomination History, 1985-1988 (Box 193)
      - American Academy of Arts and Sciences Award, 1999-2003 (Box 193)
      - Amoco Foundation Award, 1991 (Box 193)
      - Amoco Faculty Teaching Award, 1995-1996; 2 folders (Box 193)
      - Award Guidelines, 1997-1998 (Box 193)
      - David and Lucille Packard Fellowship, 1993-2000 (Box 193)
      - Distinguished Dissertation, 1990-1995 (Box 193)
      - Distinguished Faculty Achievement Award, 1995-1996; 2 folders (Box 193)
      - Distinguished Professorships, 1990-1994 (Box 193)
      - Distinguished University Professorship, 1985-1994 (Box 193)
      - Draper Prize, 1996 (Box 193)
      - Dreyfus Foundation, 1995 (Box 193)
      - Faculty and Teaching Assistant Award History (Box 193)
      - Faculty Awards, 1988-1997; 4 folders (Box 193)
      - Faculty Recognition Award, 1995-1996; 2 folders (Box 193)
      - Ford Foundation Fellowship Award, 1989-1996 (Box 193)
      - Graduate Pedagogy Award
        - 1997-1998 (Box 193)
        - 1997 (Box 193)
        - 1998 (Box 193)
        - Application/Acceptance Form (Box 193)
        - Charter and Beginning (Box 193)
        - Committees Memos, 1997 (Box 193)
        - Departmental, 1998
          - English (Box 193)
          - History of Art (Box 193)
          - Natural Resources (Box 193)
        - Department Winner, 1997 (Box 193)
        - General Communications, 1998 (Box 193)
        - Individual, 1998
          - Bhattacharyya, Sayaw (Box 193)
          - Bishop, Stephen (Box 193)
          - Chimunas, Susan (Box 193)
          - Cooks, Jamal (Box 193)
          - DeLong, Matthew (Box 193)
          - Dygraaf,Christine (Box 193)
          - Geverdt, Douglas (Box 193)
          - Nurushev, Teamour (Box 193)
          - Philosophy (Box 193)
          - Schlossberg, Marc (Box 193)
          - Slavic Department (Box 193)
          - Talsma, Valerie (Box 193)
          - Textor, Alex (Box 193)
          - Vodosek, Markus (Box 193)
          - Wang, Karen (Box 193)
          - Wilkinson, Danielle (Box 193)
        - Individual Winners, 1997 (Box 193)
        - Joint Committee Awards, 1997 (Box 193)
        - Lipschutz Weisburch Training Report, 1995 (Box 193)
        - Pedagogy Initiative, 1998 (Box 193)
        - Pedagogy Survey, 1998 (Box 193)
        - Subcommittee, 1997 (Box 193)
      - Henry Russel Award and Lecturer, 1986-1998; 2001; 9 folders (Box 193)
      - Henry Russel Award History (Box 193)
      - Hewlett Foundation Grant, 1979; 1980-1990; 2 folders (Box 193)